export const Quizdata=[
    {
    question:'which language runs in a web browser?',
    options:['java','php','javasctipt','oop'],
    answer:3
    },
    {
    question:'what does css stands for?',
    options:['central system sheet','cascading style sheet','cascasing system sheet','central style sheet'],
    answer:2
    },
    {
    question: 'Who is the father of HTML?',
    options:['Rasmus Lerdorf','Tim Berners-Lee','Brendan Eich','Sergey Brin'],
    answer:2
    },
    {
    question:' HTML stands for ___',
    options:['HyperText Markup Language',
        'HyperText Machine Language',
        'HyperText Marking Language',
        'HighText Marking Language'],
    answer:1
    },
    {
    question:'Which is used to read an HTML page and render it?',
    options:['web browser','web server','window','desktop'],
    answer:1
    },
    {
    question:'Which tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?',
    options:['head',
        '<h1>',
        '<h6>',
        'heading'],
    answer:2
    },
    {
    question:'Which is used to create Web Pages ?',
    options:['C++',
    'Java',
    'HTML',
    'JVM'],
    answer:3
    },
    {
    question:'HTML is a set of markup ___.',
    options:['tags',
    'sets',
    'attributes',
    'none of the above'],
    answer:1
    },
    {
    question:'HTML program is saved using ___ extension',
    options:['.htmn',
    '.html',
    '.htnl',
    '.htnl'],
    answer:2
    },
    {
    question:'HTML program can be read and rendered by ___',
    options:['Compiler',
    'Server',
    'Web Browser',
    'Interpreter'],
    answer:3
    }
]